(knocking on door)
Hi.
(Leonard:)Hey.
(Bernadette:)We brought snacks
for movie night.
(Penny:)Oh, great.
(Penny:)I don't suppose you also brought
napkins, clean bowls,
(Penny:)utensils and a roll
of toilet paper.
(Bernadette:)Right here.
Ah!
(Penny:)You guys are the best.
(Amy:)What's with the clothes?
(Penny:)Well, with all the new stuff
I bought for work,
(Penny:)I needed to make room
in my closet.
(Amy:)I meant why are they folded?
(Amy:)But whatever.
(Amy:)Ooh, what's this?
(Penny:)That, believe it or not,
is my prom dress.
(Bernadette:)Wow, you still have it?
(Bernadette:)I just assumed
it was balled up
(Bernadette:)in the corner
of a barn somewhere.
(Penny:)What kind of teenager
did you think I was?
(Bernadette:)Slutty.
Easy.
The word is "popular."
(Bernadette:)How was your prom?
Did you go?
(Amy:)No, but I was
on clean-up crew.
(Penny:)Aw, that's sad.
(Amy:)No, it was okay.
(Amy:)The DJ let me dance
one slow song with my mop